{
    "title": "Movie by Mahem",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "This Is Benjamin - He's A Little Bit Worried About His Future.",
            "choices": [
                "The Graduate",
                "American Pie",
                "Divorce American Style",
                "Tootsie"
            ],
            "answer": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "In Space No One Can Hear You Scream.",
            "choices": [
                "Blade Runner",
                "2001 - A Space Odessey",
                "Predator", "Alien"
            ],
            "answer": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "Who You Gonna Call?",
            "choices": [
                "Beetlejuice",
                "Gremlins",
                "The Goonies",
                "Ghostbusters"
            ],
            "answer": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "I'm Scared To Close My Eyes, I'm Scared To Open Them.",
            "choices": [
                "The Blair Witch Project",
                "The Ring",
                "Evil Things",
                "Paranormal Activity"
            ],
            "answer": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "It's Not A Rematch This Time, It's War.",
            "choices": [
                "Talons of the Eagle",
                "Kickboxer",
                "No Retreat No Surrender 2",
                "The Circuit"
            ],
            "answer": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Eight Legs, Two Fangs, And An Attitude",
            "choices": [
                "Arachnophobia",
                "Tarantula",
                "Kingdom of the Spiders",
                "Eight Legged Freaks"
            ],
            "answer": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Reality is a thing of the past.",
            "choices": [
                "The Matrix",
                "Total Recall",
                "The Terminator",
                "Tron"
            ],
            "answer": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "This Ain't No Chick FLick! AND Escape or Die Frying",
            "choices": [
                "The Road to El Dorado",
                "Shrek",
                "Chicken Little",
                "Chicken Run"
            ],
            "answer": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "Some memories are best forgotten",
            "choices": [
                "The Departed",
                "Memento",
                "Unknown",
                "Insomnia"
            ],
            "answer": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "You Won't Believe Your Eye",
            "choices": [
                "The Incredibles",
                "Monster House",
                "Finding Nemo",
                "Monsters, Inc."
            ],
            "answer": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "Before you die, you see...",
            "choices": [
                "The Evil Dead",
                "Saw",
                "The Grudge",
                "The Ring"
            ],
            "answer": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "She brought a small town to its feet and a huge corporation to its knees.",
            "choices": [
                "North Country",
                "Erin Brockovich",
                "A Civil Action",
                "Sex, Lies, and Videotape"
            ],
            "answer": 1
        }
    ]
}